outfitters.com.pk 2019-12-14

# Privacy policy OutfittersPK

Thank you for accessing our website. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. By visiting the Site directly or through another site, you accept the practices described in this Policy.

We collect personal information such as your contact information (name, e-mail address, etc.), and billing/shipping information (credit card number, visa card Number shipping address, etc.)We take responsibility for all the personal data that you provide us with, that we obtain when you subscribe to our newsletter or when you create a personal profile.

We use the information that we collect to fulfill our commitments to you and to provide you with the service that you expect. This includes sending you information and offers for marketing purposes. In order to provide you with relevant offers and information, we may analyze your personal data. We will only keep your data for as long as necessary to carry out our services to you or for as long as we are required by law. After this, your personal data will be deleted.

Outfitters may share your data information with third party or affiliates of Outfitters who perform services on our behalf or process authorized transactions. The data information we share with these companies to perform services on our behalf is protected via contractual agreements and cannot be shared.

While creating an account on our website, you will be enquired to provide a personal password. You will be required to use your chosen password for all future access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. Outfitters reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in its lone discretion.

You have the right to request access to the personal data which we may hold or process about you. You have the right to require us to correct any incorrect, incomplete or irrelevant information in your data. At any stage, you also have the right to ask us to stop using your personal data for direct marketing purposes.

We try our best to provide accurate information on our site. However, there may be times when some information on the site is inaccurate, out-of-date or incomplete. We apologize for such errors; but if we receive orders for products for which the listed cost is erroneously lower than the actual price, we will not be able to process such orders as it will not be feasible for us to sell those items below our cost or take a loss on freight charges.

The acceptance of cookies is not a requirement for visiting the Site. However, we would like to point out that the use of the "basket" functionality on the Site and ordering is only possible with the activation of cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is saved to, and, during subsequent visits, retrieved from your computer or mobile device. Ethnicities cookies to enhance and simplify your visit. We do not use cookies to store personal information or to disclose information to third parties. There are two types of cookies: permanent and temporary (session cookies). Permanent cookies are stored as a file on your computer or mobile device for no longer than 12 months. Session cookies are stored temporarily and disappear when you close your browser session.   
We use permanent cookies to store your choice of the start page and to store your details. We use session cookies when you use the product filtration function and to check if you are logged in. You can easily erase cookies from your computer or mobile device using your browser.

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. Our business changes constantly and we will continue to implement new technologies to improve the services and features we provide. As a consequence, the terms in this Privacy Policy may change also.
